Hello everyone, we are a team from the Academy of Fine Arts.
We are members of the 3D character design team from the Academy of Fine Arts.
We would like to thank MD for inviting us to share this tool with you.
We used MD to create the 3D character of the wolf-eating horse.
However, due to the unresolved project, we lost this project.
We decided to turn it into the wolf-eating horse,
which is a more modern game.
In the next 2-3 years, the usage rate of MD has dropped significantly,
which led to the invitation of us,
just like the old players and newcomers,
to explore with this tool again.
Let me introduce myself.
I am the UI designer of our center.
My name is Chen Shuyu.
I study 3D software in order to do my personal work,
so I will share my personal pictures later.
This is my A-Pack.
This is...
a picture of our elevator,
which I took and posted here.
Here is the image.
I will show you how I made the model.
This is the depth.
This is the width.
This is the length.
The clothes are made of MD.
I will first introduce my personal process.
I design first,
look for references,
create an emotion board,
draft the location,
and then make the character.
When I make the character,
I will create some...
I will create the character's identity,
and then make the 20-degree direction.
After that,
I will first make a picture for Google,
and after that,
I will make a cool pose.
After that,
I will import the MD,
the MPC format,
to make its material.
After that,
I will import it back to Blender,
make some accessories,
and then make some materials.
For the materials,
I will first make the PBR process,
and then,
for the skin,
I will make the 20-degree drawing process.
After that,
I will export it.
My final goal is to get a
better competition drawing,
so I will work on the animation.
And then,
this is the last year's
GIF.
For the GIF,
I will see my drawing
by the UNICAT commentator.
Then I will make my drawing
with the GIF to show the GIF,
and then,
I will see the result.
I will also make
some art models to compare it
with my drawing.
This is the GIF I have made.
The end.
Thank you.
Okay,
this is the GIF,
this is the GIF I have made.
So I started to draw some grass-based drafts.
Because I would draw some grass-based drafts first,
so that I could draw my own direction,
and then do a three-dimensional structure.
So it's something like this.
And then I would try my best to recreate what I had drawn.
And then I also tried to do...
I tried to do an illustration using my own three-dimensional model.
But at the end, I still liked to do a three-dimensional figure.
And then, do you think this model is very familiar?
It's the three-dimensional figure that was drawn in the FD.
And then I used Blender to make a Google map for it.
At the same time, I made some of its sound effects smaller,
and made them thinner,
so that the clothes could be shown better.
So I created its top.
The top is a software.
This is a style drawing I made.
I made a VB font.
I didn't do the mouth.
The mouth is made with a surface sheet,
and the eyes are also made with a surface sheet.
This time, I mostly talked about how to do the designs with the characteristics of MD.
My main line is to do a good-looking and fast-tracking design.
So I needed to have a sense of freedom in the design.
I didn't want to make a small high-end model like traditional modeling.
And then, MD, when it comes to changing the template, it's actually the same as making the A.I. template.
It's the same as making the A.I. A.I. template.
You use a dot to form a face.
And then, to make MD, you have to add the following things.
I'll show you how to add them later.
The first thing is to draw the template like a sketch.
You can draw some hollows here.
I like to draw hollows like this for a while.
You can also draw some shapes inside.
For example, I drew a spider web and pasted it on the sketch.
That's about it.
Thank you.
This is the effect of changing the template.
And then, it's like drawing a painting.
I drew a leaf and made a chest for it.
This is the effect that I've been using for a few years.
Next, I'll talk about the advantages of the handsome pose on the character and the clothes.
When I was a kid,
I would draw a character like this.
There was a gap line.
I would look for the feeling of this kind of visual.
I would look for some wind.
It was like...
At that time, I was more of an exaggerator.
I was more of an exaggerator.
I think it's better to be exaggerated.
A handsome pose new ways of
a handsome pose new ways of
it makes the piece look straighter
and you could add some volume to it.
板環
It can be used for flat software, or even for 3D software.
I started with the first one,
I started by adding some chacha chacha chacha,
and then added a line here.
After that, I realized that
a lot of versions seem to have a square shape,
so I decided to use a G-shape for the design.
I will also talk about
when I was making the material,
I added some particles in the brand,
to imitate the feeling of embroidery.
The details can be seen very close,
similar to the PBR process.
Then I used particles,
the method of making grass,
to brush the tree,
and so on,
to create the effect of
a three-dimensional embroidery on the fabric.
This is the first experiment
to create this effect.
This is because the top is a model,
and I made something like this.
Then,
the model here is a square shape.
my whole-body experiment
started from here.
Then I found that
if you design with a elastic thread,
there are some interesting ways
to play with the inner thread.
So I started a more free
violent modeling.
At the same time,
in the brand,
there is also a free thread,
which is a tool
to draw on the surface of the object.
I saw that the author of
Spider-Man and the Planet of the Apes
has also used this method,
to draw some details on it,
to create the effect of a three-dimensional embroidery.
Then I started to use this
to make a design.
I drew directly on it.
Here I also gave the fabric
a needle.
After the needle is pierced,
from black to white,
it can be changed.
Then,
how does the face of this pattern
form?
I used to make the original
image of the previous set,
where I didn't pierce the mouth,
but pierced the hole of the eyes.
But in this set,
I only pierced the mouth,
but didn't pierce the hole of the eyes.
I started to draw the eyes
from the shape of the face.
Then,
there is a complete opposite
to this.
This set,
this set,
I also continued to draw on it.
I continued to draw embroidery on it.
This embroidery is drawn on it,
but it is drawn really fast.
At the same time,
when I was looking for reference,
I found this kind of
similar to the effect of laser hammering,
which can be drawn on the board,
and I drew this Z-shaped line
on the inside of the line,
and then I cut it off,
and it will have this effect.
It is very smooth and satisfying.
Then,
I continued to use the same design
to make a set of
very light skin design.
Then,
here I also used the normal hair effect
to make the fur.
Here,
I added a fish net effect,
to make it look like an alien.
Then,
this set,
this is also the same set.
Here,
I drew some flames,
some light lines.
After that,
I felt that this set was a little bit weird,
so I started to make an alien.
An alien's body,
this body is from CG3,
not MD,
but it is made of real materials.
But,
the shape of the alien is different.
At that time,
I learned some MMD,
but,
later,
I excluded the MMD
from my design process,
because I felt that it was too troublesome.
And,
there is a hard movement here,
because the hand touched the clothes,
and then the clothes fell off,
so I had to cut this off
to make it look like an alien.
Then,
this set,
I also used the
G-shape design method,
and at the same time,
I added more snake-like Z-shape to it,
and added a spring to all the Z-shape,
to make it look like an alien.
I used the MD
to make it look like an alien,
and added a spring to it,
to make it look like an alien.
But,
it didn't look like an alien,
it looked like a snake.
So,
this is the result.
I continued to imitate
the feeling of a parallel universe.
Then,
I went back to the first set of design language,
and made a second language.
I still like to make this kind of language.
But, this time,
I added an emoji emoji bag.
This set is to make
a fruit theme,
plus a jeans fabric,
plus an emoji emoji bag,
plus a doban to make a scene.
And then,
all the poses are taken from a selfie angle.
I made about four sets.
This emoji
was developed by me
to learn how to do embroidery.
I used the SD card
to learn how to do it,
but later on,
I found that I could use
the AI method to do it.
This one,
the one on the shirt,
is also embroidery.
It's just that
it's a little bigger.
But, after doing the embroidery,
the result is really good.
I think this one is
the best.
I will introduce
this one,
which is very rare.
It's a design of our company's
side-design.
Because,
it's the 14th
final fantasy.
I also insisted on
designing the side design
for the 14th final fantasy.
I designed this one.
This one is a double-sided one.
Double-sided,
you can turn it over and over again.
And it also has the idea of embroidery.
And this one,
Dalian also designed
an ancient game design.
But, for the embroidery,
there is a limitation
that you can only make nine colors.
Then, we found five factories
to make the embroidery.
For the embroidery,
we made this into an AI picture.
We made five factories
to make the embroidery.
And then,
we provided them with the colors.
And then, we chose the fabric as well.
And this one,
in the game,
it's drawn in a smaller size.
And we need to do it ten times
to make the embroidery effect.
And this one is the food picture.
And then,
two years later,
I learned how to do it.
After MD,
And this one,
it's called
Adobos.
It's called
SA.
You can just
put a picture in it
and it will help you
to make the embroidery.
And you can also choose
the quality of the embroidery.
You don't need to use
such a troublesome thing
to connect the numbers.
You can do it one by one.
And then,
I want to introduce
a fashion style
that was more popular last year.
It's called
Blokunt.
It's more about
movement.
Last year,
I did it in this direction.
It's more like
Adidas.
And then,
I did it in this direction.
It's more like
a little girl.
And then,
it's almost finished.
Let's welcome
the next person.
She is the
third-person character of our company.